{"directed": false, "graph": [], "links": [{"source": "Reflections from the Women's March on Washington", "target": "Washington"}, {"source": "Reflections from the Women's March on Washington", "target": "March"}, {"source": "The TPP controversy explained", "target": "Pacific"}, {"source": "Trump withdraws US from Trans-Pacific Partnership deal", "target": "US"}, {"source": "Trump withdraws US from Trans-Pacific Partnership deal", "target": "Trans-Pacific Partnership"}, {"source": "Israel's Livni skips Belgium trip amid threat of arrest", "target": "Israel"}, {"source": "Israel's Livni skips Belgium trip amid threat of arrest", "target": "Belgium"}, {"source": "Israel's Livni skips Belgium trip amid threat of arrest", "target": "Brussels"}, {"source": "Iraq army denies taking east Mosul from ISIL", "target": "Iraq"}, {"source": "Iraq army denies taking east Mosul from ISIL", "target": "Mosul"}, {"source": "Iraq army denies taking east Mosul from ISIL", "target": "ISIL"}, {"source": "Iraq army denies taking east Mosul from ISIL", "target": "ISIL Army"}, {"source": "Uganda's School for Life: Educating out of Poverty", "target": "Uganda"}, {"source": "Uganda's School for Life: Educating out of Poverty", "target": "Poverty Can"}, {"source": "Uganda's School for Life: Educating out of Poverty", "target": "Ugandan"}, {"source": "Chief judge quits over 'begging for Gulf money'", "target": "Ahmad Hilayel"}, {"source": "Chief judge quits over 'begging for Gulf money'", "target": "Arab Gulf"}, {"source": "Chief judge quits over 'begging for Gulf money'", "target": "Gulf"}, {"source": "Outbreak of H5N1 bird flu at poultry farm in Dhaka", "target": "Dhaka"}, {"source": "Samsung blames Galaxy Note 7 fires on faulty batteries", "target": "Company"}, {"source": "Samsung blames Galaxy Note 7 fires on faulty batteries", "target": "Samsung"}], "multigraph": false, "nodes": [{"id": "Reflections from the Women's March on Washington", "score": 0}, {"id": "The TPP controversy explained", "score": 0}, {"id": "Trump withdraws US from Trans-Pacific Partnership deal", "score": 0}, {"id": "Israel's Livni skips Belgium trip amid threat of arrest", "score": 0}, {"id": "Iraq army denies taking east Mosul from ISIL", "score": 0}, {"id": "Uganda's School for Life: Educating out of Poverty", "score": 0}, {"id": "Film 'Mawlana' provokes outcry over religion and state", "score": 0}, {"id": "Chief judge quits over 'begging for Gulf money'", "score": 0}, {"id": "Outbreak of H5N1 bird flu at poultry farm in Dhaka", "score": 0}, {"id": "Samsung blames Galaxy Note 7 fires on faulty batteries", "score": 0}, {"id": "Ahmad Hilayel", "score": 0.1}, {"id": "PERSON", "score": 0.1}, {"id": "Arab Gulf", "score": 0.2}, {"id": "LOCATION", "score": 0.2}, {"id": "Belgium", "score": 0.2}, {"id": "LOCATION", "score": 0.2}, {"id": "Brussels", "score": 0.2}, {"id": "LOCATION", "score": 0.2}, {"id": "Dhaka", "score": 0.2}, {"id": "LOCATION", "score": 0.2}, {"id": "Gulf", "score": 0.2}, {"id": "LOCATION", "score": 0.2}, {"id": "Iraq", "score": 0.2}, {"id": "LOCATION", "score": 0.2}, {"id": "Israel", "score": 0.2}, {"id": "LOCATION", "score": 0.2}, {"id": "Mosul", "score": 0.2}, {"id": "LOCATION", "score": 0.2}, {"id": "Pacific", "score": 0.2}, {"id": "LOCATION", "score": 0.2}, {"id": "US", "score": 0.2}, {"id": "LOCATION", "score": 0.2}, {"id": "Uganda", "score": 0.2}, {"id": "LOCATION", "score": 0.2}, {"id": "Washington", "score": 0.2}, {"id": "LOCATION", "score": 0.2}, {"id": "Company", "score": 0.3}, {"id": "ORGANIZATION", "score": 0.3}, {"id": "ISIL", "score": 0.3}, {"id": "ORGANIZATION", "score": 0.3}, {"id": "ISIL Army", "score": 0.3}, {"id": "ORGANIZATION", "score": 0.3}, {"id": "Samsung", "score": 0.3}, {"id": "ORGANIZATION", "score": 0.3}, {"id": "Trans-Pacific Partnership", "score": 0.3}, {"id": "ORGANIZATION", "score": 0.3}, {"id": "March", "score": 0.4}, {"id": "DATE", "score": 0.4}, {"id": "Poverty Can", "score": 0.5}, {"id": "MISC", "score": 0.5}, {"id": "Ugandan", "score": 0.5}, {"id": "MISC", "score": 0.5}]}
